[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "Will this change America's mind?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "this", "change", "America", "'s", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "I feel very strongly that marriage is between a man and a woman.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "very", "strongly", "that", "marriage", "is", "between", "a", "man", "and", "a", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Did I really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "I", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Literally.", "answer_tokens": ["Literally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "How did you personally feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "personally", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "I was -- I was sitting home alone.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "sitting", "home", "alone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "What do you think this will do to the debate in America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "this", "will", "do", "to", "the", "debate", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, I mean the presidency above everything else is a bully pulpit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "the", "presidency", "above", "everything", "else", "is", "a", "bully", "pulpit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 69, "question": "I mean, does this not illustrate in my view the futility of a state system, where you can travel around America and you can be legally gay married here, not legally gay married there, legally gay married here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "does", "this", "not", "illustrate", "in", "my", "view", "the", "futility", "of", "a", "state", "system", ",", "where", "you", "can", "travel", "around", "America", "and", "you", "can", "be", "legally", "gay", "married", "here", ",", "not", "legally", "gay", "married", "there", ",", "legally", "gay", "married", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "EX", ",", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "No, it's a big --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "big", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Does this make Barack Obama a flip-flopper and does that help Mitt Romney come November?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "this", "make", "Barack", "Obama", "a", "flip-flopper", "and", "does", "that", "help", "Mitt", "Romney", "come", "November", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "I don't know whether it's going to help Mitt Romney come November.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "whether", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "help", "Mitt", "Romney", "come", "November", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "What is your reaction to what happened today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "what", "happened", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "It's astonishing what President Obama did today.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "astonishing", "what", "President", "Obama", "did", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Now I want to ask this gentleman here, does he have a problem with that?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "I", "want", "to", "ask", "this", "gentleman", "here", ",", "does", "he", "have", "a", "problem", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Well, do you have a problem with that?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "you", "have", "a", "problem", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Look, I -- the gentleman brings up the golden rule.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "--", "the", "gentleman", "brings", "up", "the", "golden", "rule", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":"], "qSentId": 147, "question": "What about the Muths?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "the", "Muths", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "And --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Do you have a problem with that, sir?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "problem", "with", "that", ",", "sir", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I find -- I find --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "find", "--", "I", "find", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", ":", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 161, "question": "You discriminate then, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "discriminate", "then", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "-- wanting to make the lifetime commitment of -- wanting to make the lifetime --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "wanting", "to", "make", "the", "lifetime", "commitment", "of", "--", "wanting", "to", "make", "the", "lifetime", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "-- with two loving Americans getting married?", "question_tokens": ["--", "with", "two", "loving", "Americans", "getting", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "CD", "VBG", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "It's absolutely very simple.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "absolutely", "very", "simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Are these the kind of marriages that you prefer?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "these", "the", "kind", "of", "marriages", "that", "you", "prefer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "To a gay couple that have been together 20 years?", "question_tokens": ["To", "a", "gay", "couple", "that", "have", "been", "together", "20", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "No, it's not just about love.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "just", "about", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Why would it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, because, as I've tried to say to you, the social science evidence is on my side, not on your side.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", ",", "as", "I", "'ve", "tried", "to", "say", "to", "you", ",", "the", "social", "science", "evidence", "is", "on", "my", "side", ",", "not", "on", "your", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "What is it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "And I say to you -- excuse me.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "say", "to", "you", "--", "excuse", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Alan", "Patricia Muth"]}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "What is the social science evidence?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "social", "science", "evidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Excuse me, Piers, look, Alan and Patricia Muth wanted to get married, they're brother and sister.", "answer_tokens": ["Excuse", "me", ",", "Piers", ",", "look", ",", "Alan", "and", "Patricia", "Muth", "wanted", "to", "get", "married", ",", "they", "'re", "brother", "and", "sister", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Bill, let's just -- let's just get back to your views of gay people, all right?", "question_tokens": ["Bill", ",", "let", "'s", "just", "--", "let", "'s", "just", "get", "back", "to", "your", "views", "of", "gay", "people", ",", "all", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "RB", ":", "JJ", "POS", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "No, we never talked about my views of gay people.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "never", "talked", "about", "my", "views", "of", "gay", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Have you got children?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "What kind of question is this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "question", "is", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 228, "question": "What would you do to them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "I would love --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Catholic Church"]}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", "CC", "JJ", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What would you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I would love them because you -- the Catholic Church teaches that all people, gay and straight, should be loved.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "them", "because", "you", "--", "the", "Catholic", "Church", "teaches", "that", "all", "people", ",", "gay", "and", "straight", ",", "should", "be", "loved", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "So, Clay, you must be pretty happy that he reacted so quickly?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "Clay", ",", "you", "must", "be", "pretty", "happy", "that", "he", "reacted", "so", "quickly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "I -- I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Clay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "How did you feel when you heard the news?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "You know, it is a little bittersweet.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "is", "a", "little", "bittersweet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "You know, really?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "IKEN: I was worried about coming on here and looking foolish tonight and there's no way that I can now because the standard has dropped to the floor.", "answer_tokens": ["IKEN", ":", "I", "was", "worried", "about", "coming", "on", "here", "and", "looking", "foolish", "tonight", "and", "there", "'s", "no", "way", "that", "I", "can", "now", "because", "the", "standard", "has", "dropped", "to", "the", "floor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Carolina"]}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 276, "question": "I mean seriously?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Well, you know, in North Carolina --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "in", "North", "Carolina", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "I mean what's it been like?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "'s", "it", "been", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "You know, I think it was an evolution, much like it was for the president.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "an", "evolution", ",", "much", "like", "it", "was", "for", "the", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Pardon me?", "question_tokens": ["Pardon", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "If you were Mitt Romney, you might be thinking they were going to hammer me over flip-flopping, I've got him here.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "you", "might", "be", "thinking", "they", "were", "going", "to", "hammer", "me", "over", "flip-flopping", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "him", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California"]}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "RB", "WRB", "NNP", "CD", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "It was shocking, especially when Proposition 8 was first on the ballot, because I felt -- I was just certain that it would never come to be, because we are California.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "shocking", ",", "especially", "when", "Proposition", "8", "was", "first", "on", "the", "ballot", ",", "because", "I", "felt", "--", "I", "was", "just", "certain", "that", "it", "would", "never", "come", "to", "be", ",", "because", "we", "are", "California", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Why do you think the critics of this care so much?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "the", "critics", "of", "this", "care", "so", "much", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, I mean, it really seems to boil down to the definition of marriage.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "really", "seems", "to", "boil", "down", "to", "the", "definition", "of", "marriage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 418, "question": "I thought, what?", "question_tokens": ["I", "thought", ",", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Yeah, that --", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Is it more ignorance than bigotry, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "more", "ignorance", "than", "bigotry", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Were you a bit fed up with Vice President Biden when he quoted a rival show, \"Will & Grace\"?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "a", "bit", "fed", "up", "with", "Vice", "President", "Biden", "when", "he", "quoted", "a", "rival", "show", ",", "``", "Will", "&", "Grace", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Do you still get that kind of reaction from anywhere that you go in your country?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "get", "that", "kind", "of", "reaction", "from", "anywhere", "that", "you", "go", "in", "your", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I personally have not had that reaction.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "personally", "have", "not", "had", "that", "reaction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "What do you personally think of the president of your country sitting there and announcing momentously that he supports gay marriage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "personally", "think", "of", "the", "president", "of", "your", "country", "sitting", "there", "and", "announcing", "momentously", "that", "he", "supports", "gay", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "EX", "CC", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "He basically just affirmed what everyone thought anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "basically", "just", "affirmed", "what", "everyone", "thought", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Did you agree with the president today?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "agree", "with", "the", "president", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "I agreed with the president today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agreed", "with", "the", "president", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNPS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "What do you think of the way the Republicans are now positioning this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "the", "way", "the", "Republicans", "are", "now", "positioning", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I think Republicans need to embrace the issue.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Republicans", "need", "to", "embrace", "the", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I think the youth were galvanized to take out their credit cards at least today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "youth", "were", "galvanized", "to", "take", "out", "their", "credit", "cards", "at", "least", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Let me start with you, Ben, yes or no?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "start", "with", "you", ",", "Ben", ",", "yes", "or", "no", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I'd say hindered.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "say", "hindered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Dana?", "question_tokens": ["Dana", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Hindered.", "answer_tokens": ["Hindered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "Elise?", "question_tokens": ["Elise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Helped.", "answer_tokens": ["Helped", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNPS", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Hilary?", "question_tokens": ["Hilary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "I think helped, no question, because Americans want their politicians to believe in themselves and in their communities.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "helped", ",", "no", "question", ",", "because", "Americans", "want", "their", "politicians", "to", "believe", "in", "themselves", "and", "in", "their", "communities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Lewis, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Lewis", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "It gets better all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "gets", "better", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lewis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "Why can't they?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "ca", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Well, you know, I don't know -- the gay couples I know have some of the longest relationships that I know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "--", "the", "gay", "couples", "I", "know", "have", "some", "of", "the", "longest", "relationships", "that", "I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "You have five kids, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "five", "kids", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "What would you do if one of them came home and said, dad, I'm gay?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "if", "one", "of", "them", "came", "home", "and", "said", ",", "dad", ",", "I", "'m", "gay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Well, we would have a conversation about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "would", "have", "a", "conversation", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120509pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "If he gets re-elected, where do you want to see a bit more grit?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "gets", "re-elected", ",", "where", "do", "you", "want", "to", "see", "a", "bit", "more", "grit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Well, I certainly would like to see a bit more grit in terms of gay issues, in terms of LGBT issues.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "would", "like", "to", "see", "a", "bit", "more", "grit", "in", "terms", "of", "gay", "issues", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "LGBT", "issues", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]